thevoiceofnation.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy | The Voice Of Nation

This policy is regarding the assemblage, usage, disclosure and transfer of your details by The Voice of Nation (TVON), its affiliate(s) and subsidiary(ies), which operate other services that might not be limited to delivery of content through any device connected with mobile or the Internet. Your continues usage of our services shall be construed as you consent to this Privacy Policy. In case you do not agree to any of the clauses or Privacy Policy as a whole, please DO NOT use our services.

Your privacy is highly important for us.

We acknowledge the privacy of the users of our services, and is determined to rationally protect it by all means. The user’s information that is gathered by us includes:

(a) Information provided by users

(b) Information automatically traced while browsing the website

(c) Information gathered from any other source (Third party)

(d) Name, Email id,Phone Number

In case you realize that the information provided by you is inaccurate or incomplete, you can rectify the same by contacting us at contact@thevoiceofnation.com We shall update your information at earliest.

**Log File Information** Limited information automatically gets collected pertaining to your device’s connection to the Internet, mobile number and IP address, every time you visit our website. Your IP address guides devices, attached to the Internet, where to send your data, like the pages you navigate. Automated information is received and logged from your browser, such as, your IP address, , operating system, type and version of browser and your log-in device..

**Data Processing**

**We shall process your data only in the lawful manner and to the extent that at least one of the following applies:**

  * **if you have given consent to the processing your personal data for one or more specific purposes;**
  * **processing is necessary in order to protect the vital interests of the data subject or of another natural person;**
  * **processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller;**

_Information You And We Share_

You share your information with us for using our services which is purely knowledge based and communicate through our Services with the people through comment, and we share your information to help us operate, provide, improve, modify, tailor, advance, understand, customize and support our Services.

We shall process or share your information with your consent only. Without your prior approval, we shall neither use your data nor share it with anyone unless required in below mentioned circumstances.

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of our organization unless one of the following circumstances applies:

  * With domain administrators

Your domain administrator will have access to your account information if your account is being managed by the domain administrators. Your domain administrator may be able to:

  * view statistics regarding your account
  * change your account password.
  * suspend or terminate your account access.
  * access or retain information stored as part of your account.
  * receive your account information in order to satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * restrict your ability to delete or edit information or privacy settings.
  *   * For legal reasons

We shall share your information only with the court of law and any other such organisation if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our organisation, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**Third Party Advertisements**

**You may come across third part advertisements while using our services. Those are the promotional advertisements of third parties and they have their personal ownership over those advertisements. We’re not responsible for the content they post. Hence, we shall not be held liable in case of any false promises made through those advertisements.**

** ** **Cookies**

To enhance the responsiveness of the website for our users, we might use “cookies”, or parallel electronic tools to accumulate information in order to allocate a unique, random numeral as a User Identification (User ID) to each visitor. This will help us understand the individual interests of every user browsing from an identified computer/device. Till the time you willingly identify yourself (through registration), we by no means can know who you are, even though we allocate a cookie to your device.

The only personal detail a cookie can contain is the information that you provide. By no means can a cookie read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers could also dole out their own cookies to your browser (in case you click on their ads), a procedure that we do not manage. We obtain and accumulate certain sorts of information whenever you communicate with us on website though any of your device.

** ** **Information Security**

We take all suitable security measures to guard against unauthorized access or modification, leak or destruction of data. These measures include in-house reviews of our data compilation, storage and dealing practices and security procedures, including apposite encryption and physical security procedures to safeguard against illegitimate access to systems on which we accumulate personal data.

All information gathered on The Voice of Nation is guardedly stored inside the Company controlled database. We store the database on servers protected behind a firewall; plus the server access remains password-protected and is stringently limited. However, despite highly efficient security measures in place, no security system can be completely impenetrable. We do not warranty the security of our database, nor can we assure that details you provide will not be interrupted while transmitting them to us over the Internet. Furthermore, obviously, any information you post in the discussion columns is accessible to anyone with the Internet access.

**External Links**

TVON contains links to other websites, which are not owned or run by The Voice of Nation. Please note that we, The Voice of Nation, are not accountable for the privacy practices of any other sites.

We request you to read the privacy statements of TVON and all websites that accumulate personally identifiable information. It also applies to the third party advertisements that may appear on our website, and we recommend you go through the privacy statements of these advertisers.

In case you have any questions or recommendations regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Intellectual Property Rights**

The Service and the trademarks (names and logos) contained on the Application, are owned by or licensed to us and are subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights under the applicable laws and international conventions. The Service is for your information and personal use only and not for commercial exploitation. The **Application Name** does not give any rights to anyone to use its IPR in any circumstance for their commercial benefits.

If you download or print a copy of the same for your own personal use, you must retain all trademarks, copyright and other proprietary notices contained in and on the Application. No trade of IPR or using the same for commercial benefit is allowed.

You agree that the Company will be entitled to all legal and equitable remedies otherwise available to it to protect the intellectual property rights, without limitation, the right to seek and obtain injunctive relief and enforce the same against you.

**Updates/Changes**

With internet being an ever evolving medium, we may possibly modify our privacy policy regularly to integrate essential changes in technology, pertinent law or any other variation. Under all cases, we reserve the right to modify (anytime) the terms of our Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use.
